

PROFILE

I am a 19-year-old **ambitious** student with an incredible **passion** for computer science since I was a kid. I love to work on creative projects, and I am accustomed to **work within a team** and I am not afraid to **have a leading role**. I am **adaptable** to any situation I undertake to achieve my objectives on the professional and personal side.

CONTACT

WEBSITE: leomercier.me

E-MAIL:

leo.mercier1@etu.unilim.fr



HOBBIES / ACTIVITIES

Learning English
Practiced 10 years of soccer
Scuba-diving
Like to travel abroad.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Driver license TOEIC 935/990

LÉO MERCIER

Second year in computer science

EDUCATION

IUT du Limousin (Limoges)

2019-Today

A two-year technical degree in computer science. Many subjects such as web design, development, project planning, accounting, management, communication.

Lycée Saint-Gatien (Tours)

2016-2019

High school and I specialized in science studies and I got my « Baccalauréat Mention Bien » which is the equivalent of **high school graduation with honors**.

EXPERIENCE

Website for an organic shop

2020

I worked in a team for a school project where we needed to create a working website for a fictional customer. I worked within a team and we delivered a final product that reached the customer expectations.

Connected greenhouse project

2017-2018

Worked on a school project where we created a fully functional greenhouse with solar panel, an automatic sunroof and a water collect system with pumps to water our plants using computer and electronics.

Robotic hand project

2016-2017

Worked on a school project which consisted of 3D printing a custom-made hand and built it with motors and I coded it to create a working hand.

SKILLS

